{
  "name": {
    "front": "localisation",
    "back": "localisation"
  },
  "actions": [
    {
      "name": {
        "front": "attach",
        "back": "ATTACH"
      },
      "label": "localisation.attach.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-link",
      "input": "object-multiple",
      "process": "link",
      "persistence": "insert",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "display",
      "priority": 0
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "detach",
        "back": "DETACH"
      },
      "label": "localisation.detach.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-scissors",
      "input": "object-multiple",
      "process": "link",
      "persistence": "delete",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "display",
      "priority": 1
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "create-alert",
        "back": "CREATE_ALERT"
      },
      "label": "localisation.create-alert.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-plus",
      "input": "none",
      "process": "custom",
      "persistence": "insert",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "none",
      "priority": 0
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "create",
        "back": "CREATE"
      },
      "label": "localisation.create.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-plus",
      "input": "none",
      "process": "custom",
      "persistence": "insert",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "none",
      "priority": 2
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "update",
        "back": "UPDATE"
      },
      "label": "localisation.update.action-label",
      "icon": "fa fa-pencil",
      "input": "object-one",
      "process": "auto",
      "persistence": "update",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "input",
      "priority": 3
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "display",
        "back": "DISPLAY"
      },
      "label": "localisation.display.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-eye-open",
      "input": "object-one",
      "process": "auto",
      "persistence": "none",
      "read-only": true,
      "io-flux": "display",
      "priority": 6
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "delete",
        "back": "DELETE"
      },
      "label": "localisation.delete.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-trash",
      "input": "object-one",
      "process": "auto",
      "persistence": "delete",
      "read-only": true,
      "io-flux": "display",
      "priority": 7
    }, {
      "name": {
        "front": "list",
        "back": "LIST"
      },
      "label": "localisation.list.action-label",
      "icon": "glyphicon glyphicon-eye-open",
      "input": "query",
      "process": "auto",
      "persistence": "none",
      "read-only": false,
      "io-flux": "display",
      "priority": 8
    }
  ],
  "links": [
    {
      "name": {
        "front": "localisation-r-balise",
        "back": "localisationRBalise"
      },
      "entity": "balise",
      "fk": {
        "baliseId": "id"
      }
    }
  ],
  "queries": [
    {
      "name": "localisation"
    }, {
      "name": "localisations"
    }
  ],
  "pk": [
    "id"
  ],
  "pkMap": {
    "id": "L"
  },
  "allowedValues": {
    "statut": [
      {
        "code": "VRAI",
        "value": true,
        "isInitial": true
      }, {
        "code": "FAUX",
        "value": false
      }
    ]
  }
}
